Let me tell you a big news, work is not being done in sports, due to the
outbreak of Corona virus,
19 thousand 751 new cases of Corona have been reported in Kerala in a day,
in 24 hours
605 people have lost their lives in Kerala,
till now more than 36 lakh people
are infected with Corona in Kerala and there are many horses, there is
panic in Maharashtra due to the Delta variant of Corona,
five people have died in Maharashtra due to the Delta Plus variant,
two in Ratnagiri, 11 in Mumbai, Beed and Raigad,
there is news of
two people from both the parties have died
in Maharashtra, details of Star Plus, a
total of 66 cases of the virus have been reported so far,
how is the place value more dangerous because it is
kept repeatedly, there is a need to be more cautious,
if we are telling you that it has the ability to spread infection
50% more than Delta through office, it
spreads the fastest, it causes 30
contagion, it is also scared because it does
not give a chance to handle trees, it can infect even after 10 back lions,
see  The most
worrying thing is that even if the vaccination has been done,
friends have taken it, the
risk of infection still remains and
even Diminutive has failed to stop Delta Plus,
one infected person can infect five to eight
people and Diminutive
Plus has been kept in the category of variant of question,
this reverse variant has spread in more than 150 countries of the world
and this is the reason why there has been success in India as well and
in Maharashtra as was being told that 66
cases have been reported, hence it is a
matter of more concern that such
cases are continuously increasing in Maharashtra.